{
    "id": "64311ecc480e457795f2a92100a6411f",
    "title": "British and American English vocabulary exercise",
    "exercises": [
        {
            "id": "b5dabcded3d44f48bcf9109b3891d9f6",
            "title": "American And British English Vocabulary",
            "questions": [
                {
                    "question": "What is the dialling code for London?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "British English",
                        "American English"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Turn off the faucet when you are not using it.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "British English",
                        "American English"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "Thatâ€™s it. Can I have the check?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "British English",
                        "American English"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "She has bought a flat in upmarket London.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "British English",
                        "American English"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Have you got a torch?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "British English",
                        "American English"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Put the garbage in the bin.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "British English",
                        "American English"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "This car runs on petrol.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "British English",
                        "American English"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "He had black pants on.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "British English",
                        "American English"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                },
                {
                    "question": "His nasty remarks made me angry.",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "British English",
                        "American English"
                    ],
                    "correct": 0
                },
                {
                    "question": "Who invented the zipper?",
                    "description": "",
                    "answers": [
                        "British English",
                        "American English"
                    ],
                    "correct": 1
                }
            ]
        }
    ]
}